Most of the time, people are kind and funny, and the most important thing is someone you feel comfortable with.
だいたい優しくて面白くて、一番大事なのは一緒にいて落ち着く人
What is it?
なんです よ
Is your current job good?
今の仕事はいいの?
My current job is really good.
今の仕事めっちゃいいです
That's amazing.
すごいなぁ
difficult.
難しい
I used to do it.
昔やってました
I'd like to go back one more time, actually.
もう一回戻りたいよ、実は
So, what is your current job or part-time job?
だから、今の仕事やバイトは何かしてるの?
I am now a full-time employee.
今、正社員です
Seriously?
マジか
Is it okay if I don't say the company name?
会社名とか言わないでいい?
Your favorite type
好きなタイプとか、
Is the person you fell in love with your type?
好 きになった人がタイプ?
Most of the time, people are kind and funny, and the most important thing is someone you feel comfortable with.
だいたい優しくて面白くて、一番大事なのは一緒にいて落ち着く人
What is it?
なんです よ
I see.
なるほど
You don't like people who care about you, right?
気遣う人は嫌だよね?
I don't like it.
嫌です
Does age matter?
歳は関係ない?
I don't like it if it's too high, and I don't like it if it's too low.
上すぎても嫌だし、下すぎても嫌だ
However, I feel like 5 years old is the limit in terms of age.
でも、範囲的には5歳が限界なのかなって感じだ
I've never dated someone so distant.
そんな離れた人と付き合ったことない
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうだね
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳やんか、
I guess he's about 25 years old.
25歳 くらいのってことやねん
that's right.
そうです
Until recently, I was working part-time at a flower shop.
ちょっと前まで花屋でバイトしてたじゃん
I had piled up flowers.
積んでたじゃん、花を
I think that one suited her better.
あっちの方が似合ってたと思う
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yes, I'm happy.
はい、嬉しいです
Why did you quit and become a full-time employee?
なんでやめて正社員だったの?
It's human relationships.
人間関係です
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Are you going to play futsal at night?
夜はフットサルするんだったっけ?
That's dangerous, isn't it?
やばいですよね
Where do you play futsal?
フットサルってさ、どこでしてんの?
Is it futsal?
フットサルですか?
Is there one?
あるの?
Where to do it?
やるとこ?
There are places to do it, but I haven't decided on a specific location.
やるとこありますけど、そんなに場所決まってなくて
Do you feel like going there when you are called?
呼ばれたらそこに行く感じ?
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
It's been quite a while since we met.
俺、出会ってからだいぶ経つじゃん
What I thought from the beginning was that the style was one-dimensional.
最初から思ってたことは、スタイルが1次元デベチ
It's not even debechi.
デベチでもないです
Wait a minute, let's do it.
ちょっと待って、しよう
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ ー、すごい
Surely you're popular, right?
確かに、モテんでしょ?
Are you popular?
モテなの?
No, you're popular, right?
いや、モテんでしょ
How many people have experience?
経験人数、どれぐらいあんの?
More than 10 people.
10人以上
Some people will tell you.
どれ人には言われます
When was the last time you did it?
最近、実際いつしました?
Recently, yesterday.
最近は、昨日
Yesterday?
昨 日?
boyfriend?
彼氏?
Are you there?
いるんですか?
I think it's a good idea if you have free time.
暇だったら合う感じです
I'll definitely look into it though.
超、見ていくけど
I don't think I usually turn the camera around to take pictures.
カメラ、普段回して撮影なんかしないと思うんだけど
There are some people who take camera shots, and some people who do it with their boyfriends.
カ メ撮りとか、彼氏とする人もいるけど
I won't.
しないや
I know you're nervous.
緊張するの分かるから
Okay, okay, relax.
まあまあまあ、リラックスしてね
I'll go there.
そっち行くから
Is your current job good?
今の仕事はいいの?
My current job is really good.
今の仕事めっちゃいいです
Is it really good?
めっちゃいい?
Do you think you can continue there?
そこはもう続けれそう?
I think I can continue.
続けれそうです
Good thing this time.
よかったな、今回は
I've never had a boyfriend.
ずっと彼氏作らないんやな
Why?
なんでな?
I thought I'd like to play a little more.
もうちょっと遊びたいなと思って
What makes it stand out is its style.
際立ってるもん、やっぱスタイルのさ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I understand that.
それは分かる
I'm still young.
若いもんだって、まだ
I want to play with young children.
若い子遊びたいんです
I understand, I understand.
分かる分かる
You can do whatever you like.
好きにしたらいいんだよ
I was actually listening to a sex friend just now, how many people were there?
今、実際セフレで聞いてたけど、 何人いたの?
Is it really just one person?
それはやっぱ一人?
But I like it a lot, don't I?
でも結構好きなんじゃない?
It's not my favorite.
本命ではないです
Is your favorite sex friend?
本命では自分のセフレ?
Do you want to cut it off once you meet the person you love?
本命の人と付き合ったらもう、 切る?
I'll cut it.
切るよ
I usually go back to being friends.
普段、友達に戻ります
Don't block with your uncle.
おじさんとブロックとかしないでね
Don't do it.
しないで
yeah?
ん?
Have you come?
来たよ?
I'm here.
来たよ
I was suddenly nervous.
急に緊張してました
It hurts so much.
すごく痛い
Take off your mask.
マスク取らせよ
This is amazing.
すごい、これ
How many cups are there?
何カップあるの?
It's C.
Cです
C?
It just looks bigger.
大きく見えるだけです
That's amazing.
すごいなぁ
Louis has good style.
ルイちゃんはスタイル良いわ
It's stylish.
ス タ イル良いわ
I like the style.
スタイル良いわ